Guide to the Clara Fraser Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Clara Fraser papers, 1923-1998; 3187-003; 20.61 cubic feet 22 boxes
  - Fraser job correspondence after return to City Light, 1982-1986; Series 15
    - Correspondence and reports July-December, 1984 (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 17/18)
- Clara Fraser papers, 1991-1997; 3187-004; 1.92 cubic feet 2 boxes
  Content includes correspondence, clippings, leaflets, conference, plenum, and conference information, tours and travel papers, and notes.
  Donated by Helen Gilbert, who was custodian of Clara Fraser's RW records and transferred from the Radical Women Seattle Office records
  - Misc., 1980-1992; Series 1
    - Staff, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - N.O., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - PSWU, 1995 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Bay Area, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - LA Branch, 1990 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - NYC, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Portland Branch, 1990 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Seattle, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - CCC, 1990 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - $ (Finances), 1987 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - FS, 1990, 1995 (Box-folder 1/11-12)
    - Australia, 1990 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Recipes, 1990 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Recipes, newspaper clippings, 1991 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Finances, clippings, correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - General Correspondence, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - To-Read: Priority, 1989, 1995 (Box-folder 1/18-19)
    - Obituaries, 1988 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Correspondence (To-Do), 1989 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Course Outline, 1991 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Narcissim, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - "Turning Point" Ellen Goodman, undated (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Natural Superiority of Women, 1979 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Spec. Supp. No 2, 1980 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - PW/NEC Papers, 1979 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - CSS suggestions on Manifesto Editing, 1978 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - CSS trip tp Seattle, 1990 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - 1st Draft Introducing the FSF, 1977 (Box-folder 1/30)
    - Misc. Notes, 1979 (Box-folder 1/31)
    - Women as Leader, 1972 (Box-folder 1/32-33)
    - Emancipation of Women, 1973 (Box-folder 1/34)
    - 1st Draft Report, 1974 (Box-folder 1/35)
    - CRSP Documents, 1983 (Box-folder 1/36)
    - "Backwardness" Article, 1980 (Box-folder 1/37)
    - Food Planning - clippings, undated (Box-folder 1/38)
    - Misc. Material, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 1/39)
    - CF's Meeting with Gloria, 1991 (Box-folder 1/40)
    - Important Press Articles, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 1/41)
    - Press - Anti-Nazis March, 1992 (Box-folder 1/42)
    - San Francisco, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 1/43)
    - Freeway Hall Case, 1992 (Box-folder 1/44)
    - FHC Docs to Read, 1992 (Box-folder 1/45)
  - Leaflets, Series 2
    - Leaflets, 1984-1996 (Box-folder 1/46-48)
  - Conferences/Plenums/Conventions, Series 3
    - Conferences/Plenums, 1996 (Box-folder 1/49)
    - FSP National Convention, 1987 (Box-folder 1/50)
    - Pol. Res. Edit, 1987 (Box-folder 1/51)
    - FSP Convention, 1988 (Box-folder 1/52)
    - Conv. Docs, 1989 (Box-folder 1/53)
    - Nicaragua Document, 1988 (Box-folder 1/54)
    - FSP National Convention, 1988 (Box-folder 1/55)
    - FSP Convention, 1991 (Box-folder 1/56)
    - Convention Planning, 1991 (Box-folder 1/57)
    - FSP Convention, 1993 (Box-folder 1/58-60)
    - NC Plenum, 1996 (Box-folder 1/61)
    - Plenum, 1996 (Box-folder 1/62)
    - FSP National Convention Plenum, 1996 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - FSP Convention, 1997 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Convention Finances, 1997 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Plenum, 1998 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - FSP National Committee Plenum, 1998 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - NCCC Plenum - Food, Budget, Agenda, 1994 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - FSP National Plenum, 1992 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - NC Plenum, 1992 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Women & Gender Conference / S. Africa, 1990 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Brodine/Weiss, Series 4
    - Weiss Library, 1988 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - K. Brodine Estate, 1988 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Karen Memorial, 1988 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Karen B. Arrangements, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Tours/Travel, Series 5
    - Traveling Comrades Itineraries, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Cuba Reading List for Delagates to Cuba, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Nancy K's Seattle Visit, 1995 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Cuba - Yolanda, 1994 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Cuba - Doug, 1993 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - NRW Eastern Europe Tour, 1994 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - NRW Eastern Europe Tour, 1993 (Box-folder 2/20-21)
    - Charles Moran Visit, 1994 (Box-folder 2/22)